springwidgets.com 2006-12-31

# SpringWidgets : Privacy

## SpringWidgets Privacy Policy

_Effective as of March 21, 2006_

Fox Interactive Media, Inc. ("FIM") is part of the News America Group, which has adopted a set of Privacy Principles available at http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html applicable to all its U.S.-based companies.  FIM operates the Internet Web site located at www.thespringbox.com.  FIM has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how  we collect, use and share personally identifiable information ("PII") we obtain from and about individuals located in the U.S.  FIM operates general audience Web sites, and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age. From time to time, FIM may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our Web sites or technology.  If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Policy.  Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices.   If FIM materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change.

**COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ("PII") BY FIM.**   
**General**. FIM collects personally identifiable information ("PII" -- that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number) in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats or bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information.  We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties. 

**Cookies**. Cookies are small bits of information that the FIM Web sites place on the hard drive of your computer.  Cookies remember information about your activities on our site(s) and enable FIM to make your visits to our site(s) more enjoyable.  For example, cookies can store your password for easy logon to a site you have previously visited, can save your preferences for a personalized home page or can track the items you have placed in your "shopping cart" during a visit to our online store.  Information about your activities on FIM sites and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.

Third party advertisements displayed on FIM sites may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers.  FIM does not control these cookies and visitors to our Web site(s) should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or   
advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.  See the "Notice" section below for more information on third party advertisements.   
FIM may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of our Web site(s) to PII obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to provide you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on FIM Web sites may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences.  However, if FIM wishes to combine your personal and cookie or click stream information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent. 

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely.  However, without cookies you may not have access to certain features on News America Group’s Web site(s), such as the Fox Movie Channel Backlot. 

**NOTICE: FIM WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES**   
When you voluntarily provide PII to FIM, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses FIM will make of the information.  At the time you provide your PII, FIM will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII, including whether we will share it with outside companies (See “Choice” below).  This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and therefore may want to share your personal information, provided you have given FIM permission to do so (See "Use" below). 

Sometimes we collect PII from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form.  Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us. 

FIM’s Web site(s) may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a FIM logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by FIM (for example, the co-sponsored chat pages, or advertising sponsor pages).  FIM's Web site(s) also carry advertisements from other companies.  FIM is not responsible for the privacy practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our sites or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left a FIM site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you. 

FIM’s Web site(s) may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with FIM  (i.e., that are part of the News America Group). Although all News America Group entities adhere to the group’s Privacy Principles located at http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html, visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy. 

Some of the advertisements that appear on FIM's Web site(s) are delivered to you by national Internet advertising companies such as Doubleclick and 24/7Real Media. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our sites, including information about the banner ads they display, any cookie they place on your computer and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit:  

**CHOICE: FIM WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII**  
FIM will not use the PII you  provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted, or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with FIM (i.e., not part of the News America Group), unless we obtain your permission. 

**USE: FIM'S USE OF PII**  
FIM will use your PII provided under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy.  If FIM obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy.  FIM may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us, that is, are part of the News America Group of companies.  Provided you have given us permission, FIM may also share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with FIM, but would like to send you information about their products and services.  For example, some of the companies who supply prizes for FIM's contests may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to FIM viewers.  However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third parties when PII is collected.  Moreover, we will never share your credit card information with third parties except those FIM uses to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through FIM Web sites.   
FIM employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII.  FIM may share your PII with outside  contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses), but they may only use your PII to provide FIM with a specific service and not for any other purpose. 

FIM may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows FIM to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our Web sites.  Your non-PII and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished.  These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose.  Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with FIM’s advertisers and business partners.

There may be instances when FIM may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of FIM, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our Web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process.  In addition, if FIM sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, FIM may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction. 

**SECURITY: FIM PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII**  
FIM uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, FIM uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. Passwords and other sensitive information stored by FIM are encrypted both in transit and when stored within FIM’s online databases. 

**ACCESS: HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII**  
FIM has implemented  procedures for you to access, correct or delete your PII.   If you are a registered user at FIM’s Web site, you can view and change your user preferences by following the procedure detailed below.

To access your PII write to the FIM Internet Privacy Information at Fox Interactive Media, Inc., Business and Legal Affairs,  407 N Maple Drive, Beverly Hills, California 90210, requesting a listing of the PII that is on file that you have provided or that has been obtained from a third party.  FIM will provide you with a list of your PII within thirty  (30) calendar days from receipt of your request.  There may be certain instances when FIM may not be able to provide the PII, such as when access would violate the privacy of another individual or when access is prohibited by law.

In the event the PII on file is incorrect, you may correct the PII by sending a written request for correction to FIM Internet Privacy Information at Fox Interactive Media, Inc., Business and Legal Affairs, 407 N Maple Drive, Beverly Hills, California 90210, including (1) all of the incorrect PII, (2) the corrections that you wish to make to your PII, and (3) your signature authorizing such changes.  FIM will then correct the PII in its database and send a written confirmation to you within forty-five (45) business days.  

If for any reason you wish to stop all future communications from this site, you may send an e-mail with the word "Privacy" in the subject line to FIMprivacy@fox.com, or write to FIM Internet Privacy Information at Fox Interactive Media, Inc., Business and Legal Affairs, 407 N. Maple Drive, Beverly Hills, California 90210, requesting that your PII be permanently removed from this site’s database. FIM will send a written confirmation of such removal to you within thirty (30) calendar days of receipt of your request.  E-mails sent to  FIMprivacy@fox.com for purposes other than communication about PII may not be acknowledged or responded to. 

**REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO CONTACT FIM ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS**  
If you have concerns regarding privacy, your use of the FIM Web sites, or the collection and use of PII, you may contact the following FIM representative: Sean Chuang   
Fox Interactive Media, Inc.  
Privacy Liason, Business & Legal Affairs  
407 N Maple Drive  
Beverly Hills, California 90210  
Telephone: (310) 969-7200  
e-mail: FIMprivacy@fox.com   
You may also request a written response to your concerns, which will be made no later than thirty (30) days after you contact FIM. ****
